[sweet airy music]
♪ Sorry I'm gonna leave ♪
♪ I'm driving so fast ♪
♪ Tell me, why you ♪
♪ Come into me and say ♪
♪ You want me again ♪
♪ Everyone who leaves me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'll be missing you ♪
♪ Together, together ♪
[mellow music]
Can you stay over?
[Yeon-su] This is why…
this is why we had to break up.
NOVEMBER, 2008
Yeon-su, let's grab a bite.
Oh, sorry. I'm not too hungry right now.
Oh, come on. I'll get you banana milk.
Come on.
No, really, I'm fine. It's okay.
- You can go ahead. It's cool.
- Okay.
Yo, Ji-yeon, hurry up.
Let's get a move on.
I'll see you.
[girl] Come on, hurry up!
Not like she'll ever come.
Why bother, right?
[Ji-yeon] Keep it down. She can hear you.
[girl] Why do you care about her so much?
That self-centered princess
doesn't like you.
She doesn't even know you exist.
She's right. Think about it.
Yeon-su's never bothered
treating us or anything.
We always bought her stuff.
Still, it wasn't like she asked us
to buy her any of those things.
It's called being shameless.
She still accepted them
every single time without hesitation.
[girl] Remember the last time?
You always gave her a birthday gift…
[Yeon-su] I absolutely hate being poor.
The worst part is,
I can't be generous or return favors.
Our family's been poor
ever since I was born.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do it either.
[girl] Whatever. It's cool.
Don't worry about it.
[Yeon-su] It made making real friends
or hanging out with them
uncomfortably difficult.
As a young girl, it was painful.
I'd always be hurting inside.
But I guess it was okay.
Grandma.
You're here again. I told you not to come.
Just go straight home and wait for me.
Are you kidding me?
You want me home alone, all bored?
Good grief.
[Yeon-su] It was okay, I had something
precious that I wanted to protect.
[Ja-gyeong] You hands are freezing.
Have you eaten?
[Yeon-su] Were you extra busy today?
[Ja-gyeong] No, not at all.
- [boy 1] Look at her skirt.
- [boy 2] She's obviously a teacher's pet.
Hey, look at her shoes.
Even my mom wouldn't…
[Yeon-su] That's why I decided
to completely ignore everyone.
Call it being self-centered or whatever.
Simply put, it was more convenient.
[principal] I know a lot of you
are excited for spring.
Despite the weather becoming much cooler,
I would like to thank you all
for being here on this very special day.
Hey. Turn around.
[principal] Seeing all of you here,
I remember standing
in the school field 34 years ago.
[Yeon-su] I was like that all the way,
until I met Choi Ung.
["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim playing]
I'll kill you…
If you tell anyone
that we're dating, I'll kill you.
And I don't want you bothering me either.
My studies and
getting into university come first.
Likewise, same thing goes for you.
You got that?
Okay.
[sighs]
Is there anything you wanna say to me?
- [rain pattering]
- ["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim playing]
Got plans tomorrow?
["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim playing]
[chuckles softly]
[Yeon-su] The sole person
who helped me close my eyes
and escape from reality,
Choi Ung.
- Did you sleep well?
- Mm-hmm.
- How long did you wait?
- I didn't. I just got here.
[Yeon-su] So they're both symbolic
and represent specific things.
The difference between those two…
"According to this,
the population of the village…"
[groans]
Why am I dozing off?
- "Ever since the 1960s…"
- Mm-hmm.
- "The rapid industrialization of…"
- Uh-huh.
SEO-YEON UNIVERSITY
2012 ADMISSION RESULT
[gentle music]
[Yeon-su laughs happily]
CONGRATULATIONS
NAME: CHOI UNG
MAJOR: ART AND DESIGN
LET'S GO OUTSIDE
[dramatic sigh]
[soft gentle music]
- [Ung] Yeon-su.
- [door closes]
What?
- Man, what are you eating?
- Gimbap.
Oh, well. So much for this then.
[chuckles]
Kimchi fried rice, cherry tomatoes.
Did you really make this?
Yeah, of course. Wasn't really that hard.
["Red String of Fate"
by Kim Kyung Hee playing]
- Not so great?
- No, it is.
Exactly.
[Ung chuckles]
- No, I didn't. What are you talking about?
- [rain pattering]
When did I let my guard down?
You were looking all excited
when those girls
were acting really friendly around you.
Tell them to show a little bit of respect.
[Ung] Yeah, yeah, I know.
[Yeon-su] I'm just upset because you were
wasting your time with those kids.
I'm sorry.
[Yeon-su] Oftentimes,
I was yearning for a relief
from the practicality of it all.
COVER LETTER
It gave me
that comforting escape from reality.
[sighs]
Are you done?
Not yet.
I still have a few left to send out.
Do you need it right away?
What do you mean?
I mean, instead of getting a 9-to-5 job,
you can continue to study more
and land a better job in the future.
Except I don't have any time for that.
I need to get a job right now,
gotta become a full-time employee.
You get a job. Then what?
Well, I'm going to save up money so
my grandma won't have to work anymore.
- Is that it?
- What?
I mean, you managed to get scholarships,
while working part-time,
you've been breaking your back
juggling studies and work.
I just thought you'd be aiming
for something a little bigger than that.
[soft music]
[Yeon-su] I wanna live
as well as the average person.
That was my dream for the longest time.
I consider that a success.
Could it be
that maybe this isn't the dream I want?
And you?
What do you plan to do afterwards?
Me? Uhm…
I don't really have a plan.
You're good at drawing
and you enjoy doing it.
You could do that for a living.
[inhales]
I'm going to keep that as a hobby.
[Ung] What I want
is to bask in the sun during the day
and lay underneath a lamp
at night time. That's it.
A stressful life just isn't for me.
[Yeon-su] Perhaps it's destiny.
I was never given a choice to begin with.
[Ung] To be honest,
I'm content with my life.
I got my family and you.
[gentle music]
[Yeon-su] But life often slaps you awake
when you open your eyes.
It's even more cruel,
that ruthless monster called reality.
Why us?
Why do we need to pay the debt instead?
I've never even met…
[inhales shakily]
…this man who's…
who's supposedly my uncle.
[Ja-gyeong] Yeon-su…
Oh, my child.
I really wish that…
[sobbing]
I was only poor enough
to the point that I…
could at least handle it.
[soft somber music]
[driver] We're going now.
[engine starts]
[Yeon-su] Reality sneered
at my false dreams.
Hello, what is it?
[shocked gasp]
[co-worker] Yeon-su, wait!
[Yeon-su] And before I knew it…
[groans]
…just like that,
it was suffocating the life out of me.
[Ung] I'm not gonna go.
[professor] You do realize
this is every student's dream, right?
Do you have any idea
how much talent you have?
I'm sure you've noticed
that you've improved.
And that's only
after being there for six months.
Exactly, that was only six months.
Living there for a few years,
that's a different story.
Being there all by myself
isn't what I want.
Seriously? Is that your reason, huh?
Just think about it,
you can draw all the buildings you love,
and you can push yourself even further.
[sucks teeth]
What's the matter?
Don't you have any ambition?
[chuckles softly]
No. I don't.
I'm not interested in striving
for success or any of that crap.
[Ung] Someone more desperate
deserves that opportunity.
[professor scoffs]
Unbelievable.
[phone buzzing]
SEO-YEON UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
INPATIENT BILL
[somber music]
[door slams]
[door opens]
Oh, wow. When did you get here?
Something's different.
You don't normally wait for me at all.
Are we gonna get lunch? What do you want?
Wanna head out now?
[chuckles softly]
["There For You" by Kim Na Young playing]
[Yeon-su] That's why…
that's the reason
why we couldn't be together…
[Ung] Why do we have to break up?
[Yeon-su] Because our realities
were just way too different.
You always break up with me first.
[Yeon-su] Rather, it was 'cause
my reality was pathetic.
Am I the easiest thing to throw away
among the things you have?
No.
But you're the only one…
that I can get rid of.
["There For You" by Kim Na Young playing]
Why are you doing this?
[Yeon-su] Come to think of it…
maybe it was because
I couldn't even handle my own reality.
[Ung] Give me reason.
[Yeon-su] To be honest…
[Ung] Give me just one reason
why we can't be together.
To be completely honest, I was afraid
someday you'd eventually notice
this inferiority complex of mine.
EPISODE 6
PRIDE AND PREJUDICE
["There For You"
by Kim Na Young continues]
[soft groan]
[Ung] I could have sworn
I was working in my studio.
[groans]
[clunking in distance]
[clunking continues]
[both yelping]
Jeez, you scared me to death!
What the hell!
Don't sneak up on me like that.
- When did you get here?
- Just a while ago.
I thought you'd have trouble
sleeping again. I was worried.
Sleep some more. You didn't get enough.
Hey, what time did I go to bed?
How the hell would I know that?
[groans softly]
[groans, sucks teeth]
How'd I doze off like that?
- I can't believe I slept so well.
- Well, that's good to hear.
Your stopwatch stopped
a bit over 10 p.m. last night.
- Probably around then.
- Maybe.
- Did you take sleeping pills?
- Hmm.
[sighs]
I wondered why you slept
on the sofa instead of your bed.
[Ung] What is that thing?
[soft music]
Bro, you completed 95 hours.
[Eun-ho] Guess you must be
in your element.
You look amazing today.
Hey. What time did you get here again?
Me? Around 7:30 a.m.
Was I alone just then?
- [Eun-ho] Wrong, bro.
- You mean…
I meant not just then.
You've always been alone.
- Oh, screw you.
- [Eun-ho] Oh, that's right.
Ji-ung's gonna be dropping by
some time today,
to edit the footage of you working.
Also, he's gonna be doing
some filming here and there,
specifically the live drawing show.
Let's show him
just how charming you can be.
How awesome you look when you're drawing.
You're no longer the pitiful boy, right?
- [knocks on table]
- Are you listening?
God, how long has it been
since I slept this well?
That good, huh? Didn't wake up at all?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good. That's great.
That's really good.
Means you'll be in great condition.
[sighs]
[Ung] If that's true,
what's this unsettling feeling I have?
[uneasy music]
Honey, it's the weekend,
what are you doing up so early?
That opening ceremony
I've been working so hard on
- these past few weeks is today.
- Oh, really? That's today?
- [Yeon-su] Sit down, grandma.
- Oh, gosh.
Time sure does fly fast.
If you have some time later,
come and visit with grandma Ji-na.
That's okay. I don't want to distract you.
You've worked so hard on that project.
I'm sure you did a fantastic job.
You're the only person in the world
who appreciates me.
Oh, this girl. You know what I heard?
[clears throat]
I heard somewhere that the welfare center,
they're actually accepting
job application forms.
I think I should give it a go.
What? You're kidding me, right?
You must be out of your mind. No way!
Forget it. You're no spring chicken,
I'll tell you that.
I'm bored. That's all.
It's driving me nuts.
I'm stuck in the house all day,
it's sucking the life out of me.
I'm gonna die of suffocation.
There's plenty of stuff for you to do.
Hang out at the senior citizen center--
No, thank you.
There's nothing for me there.
Unless you want me to die of boredom.
Just a bunch of sick, old people
waiting for death.
That's the thing,
you should work on your temper.
- That's why you have no friends.
- [stammers]
What was that? You think
I'm some kind of rabid pit bull?
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
Just thought I'd let you know.
Come on. What if you collapse
in the middle of work?
I can't…
I'm afraid of staying home.
That's what'll ruin me mentally.
What's the disease old people get, huh?
Dementia, that one.
Hey, I'm just being cautious.
I'm not demented yet.
I'm clearheaded
compared to other people my age.
Yeah, no one, I mean no one
can hold a candle to your grandma.
So don't worry about a thing.
Go and eat up.
- Not really worried or anything.
- [clears throat]
Then why are you staring at me
like I'm about to croak?
Not very comforting.
I'm just upset
because it breaks my heart, you know.
You've been working your entire life,
without so much as a vacation.
Can't you just
take it easy once in a while?
What are you talking about?
It doesn't get easier than this.
You cook and prepare my meals
and everything else that I need.
All I do is put my feet up.
Oh, boy, it's so tough. Someone help me.
I'm so exhausted.
[Ja-gyeong] Now, go and eat up.
Enough with this nonsense.
On one condition…
don't do anything demanding.
If you only have to work
for like a few hours a day,
then fine, I'll think about it.
You're acting ridiculous, hmm?
Who do you think you are, young lady?
Do you want me to start calling you mom?
Damn straight.
I'm pretty much your legal guardian.
Better not cross me if you know
what's good for you, young lady.
[chuckles]
You should hear yourself.
- Honey, wait.
- Huh?
- [Chang-sik] Ho.
- What in the world are you wearing?
- Chang-sik, look.
- Not bad. What'd you think?
- This won't do.
Go back and put the other necktie.
The red one
will look better with this suit.
Hi. Have you guys seen
the restaurant owners?
They look like you,
but completely the opposite.
I'm glad you're here. Look at us.
Be honest. How do we look?
Tell us what you think.
Overall, you look like
a couple of Hollywood producers
who live in a wealthy neighborhood.
- I barely recognize you two.
- [both chuckle]
[gasps]
It's for a special occasion.
Ung is going to be
putting on a performance.
That boy's been constantly putting on
a performance 24-7 since he was a kid,
don't know why
you have to get all dressed up for it.
He's not gonna be putting on
some kind of an act, you jackass.
Ung's gonna draw something special
in front of a live audience
and there'll be a huge crowd.
Eun-ho came by last time
and told us about it.
He said we had to come.
To think that our son
never even bothered inviting us.
We still have a lot of time
before it starts, you know.
We need to make sure
to sit at the front row.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, my goodness.
Wait. Honey, we need
to pick up the rice cakes!
I almost forgot! We need to go so we can
pick up and give them the rice cakes.
Wait. Trust me, you oughtta just
hand them out to your neighbors instead,
unless you want him to faint out there.
Still, we need to show
at least some sort of courtesy.
They're going all the way over there
- to watch him draw.
- That's right.
Let me make this clear.
Those people need him more than you think.
They practically begged him to draw.
Everything's all set for him and
he'll pretty much be treated like a king.
My goodness. Is that true?
[excited squeal]
My gosh!
Did you hear that, you fool, huh?
They begged my son to draw for them.
He's important to all those people.
Wait, that's why
he's drawing for them right?
Yep, that's how popular
and competent he is.
[delighted chuckles]
Anyway, you don't have to rush over there.
So just take your time, don't worry.
[guests chatting]
[bright music]
[sighs]
We're at the tail-end
of this long-term project.
D-day is finally here, guys.
- [snaps fingers]
- Oh, that's right.
We should go and grab something to eat
before the others arrive at least.
That's how I believe we'll get through--
- Good idea, except there's no time.
- He's right.
Today is gonna be quite a hectic day.
Why don't we conduct
our final meeting for this over lunch?
I'll call and make the order right now.
No, let me. You all good with sandwiches?
- Yes.
- Hell yeah.
- Oh…
- [quirky music]
Should… should I just get
the same thing for all of us?
Actually, I'm on a diet.
I'll have wheat bread, roast chicken,
olive oil, and pepper, please.
I'd like the steak and cheese sub.
No pickles for me.
- I can't ever eat pickles.
- And for me…
What was that sauce we had
from the last time we ate?
I wrote it down somewhere.
All right, why don't you
let me do it instead?
You'll have what you normally have, right?
Sure.
[quirky music fades]
[yawns]
Ms. Kook, are you doing okay?
You've been looking quite exhausted.
[exhales]
I'm all right.
[Ye-in] Like you asked us to do,
we've organized two
separate press conferences
for Nu-a and Go-oh later.
We've estimated that Jean Ferrat
should be arriving
around the time the drawing show ends.
- He'll come straight from the airport.
- Okay. Thank you very much.
Do you know what time
Go-oh will arrive here? Just an estimate?
[Ung] Wanna sleep over?
[soft music]
[Ye-in] Uhm, Ms. Kook?
- Right. Don't worry. I'll ask him.
- Thanks.
[phone buzzing]
Oh, also, it looks like
Mr. Jang just arrived on the first floor.
I see.
Shouldn't you go greet him?
I'll see him once this thing starts.
Enjoy your meal, guys. We'll meet
at the front door in exactly 30 minutes.
Gotta make some last-minute checks
on the second floor.
- Okay. You got it.
- Understood.
[Ji-ung] Today's interview is gonna be
about you as an artist.
Your creative process. Feel free
to talk about your occupation and such.
What do you mean? Like what?
Like your thoughts
that are embedded in your work,
your life in general
as a person who creates art for a living.
Or maybe your goals
and plans for the future.
[Ung breathes in sharply]
I don't really have any.
Can we just
skip to the next question, please?
All right, then. Uh…
Tell me how you began drawing.
Like, what moment got you into it?
There's no story to tell.
[dopey music]
Okay, fine. You can say that then.
Hold on. That's gonna
make him seem like a simpleton.
Doesn't matter, it's the truth.
No sugarcoating. Be true to yourself.
[Ji-ung] Here we go.
[Eun-ho sighing]
We're almost there now.
Aren't you nervous?
- Hmm?
- In a way, this is kinda like your debut.
Your big introduction. Ta-da!
Your very first public appearance. Crazy.
Aren't you nervous?
If I say yes, are you gonna cancel it?
No way in hell. Hang in there, dude.
Oh, okay. I got just the song
for situations like this.
- [beeping]
- Play "Island" by NJ, please.
[song starts playing]
Oh, God, I'm so glad.
You're finally out of your cave.
I was never in a cave, dumbass.
You actually were. Don't deny it.
To be honest, I was worried sick
that you'd have trouble sleeping,
and you'd become even more
depressed and anxious
ever since Yeon-su
came back into your life.
But no need to mull over it.
In the end, this is all thanks to her.
Future's looking even brighter now.
You would have never done this
if I came up with it.
[Ung exhales]
Anyway, I hope you'll enjoy doing this
and maybe even continue
working with others out in the open.
Then you'll become
even more famous, get a lot more work,
and rake in all the moolah.
That being said, what's your take
on giving your outstanding manager
a raise after this?
I'm passionately against it.
Hmm. I see. Then let's take our time
and discuss that topic more
sometime down the road.
- What?
- And here we are.
[cheery pop music]
Go and head up to the second floor first.
Your green room will be there.
I'll go look for parking,
and I'll bring your stuff over.
You can forget about the raise.
You already have your welfare--
Oh, boy, we're holding back the road.
Go on, they're getting angry back there.
[Ung grunts]
- See you later.
- All right, I'll see you soon.
[cheery pop music]
LIVE DRAWING SHOW
GO-OH, NU-A
SEON SHOP OPENING DRAWING SHOW
GO-OH
[Ye-in] We should run it
by Ms. Kook before we do it.
Mr. Kang, have you seen Ms. Kook?
[Ji-un] I saw her heading
to the second floor.
- [Ye-in] I see. Let's check the showroom.
- [Ji-un] Okay.
["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim playing]
[chuckles softly]
[Ung] She always looked
perpetually mad whenever we're together.
I think…
I finally appreciate Yeon-su
for who she is.
["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim playing]
We already interviewed Ung this morning.
We just need Yeon-su's now.
You don't need much,
just get some rough footage.
Once the show begins,
make sure to focus on him.
Intern, I want you to stay with her.
Sure, you can count on that, sir.
Should I interview her
before the event starts?
No, I'll do it.
We have a meeting
back at the office later,
- so let's pick up the pace.
- [Chae-ran] Understood, sir.
["Summer Rain" by Sam Kim continues]
[clears throat]
- Oh.
- I'm sorry, is this the waiting area?
[Yeon-su] What the… It's Ung.
When did he even get here?
[exhales]
Great. What should I say?
Do I wanna mention last night?
About yesterday…
You were at my place, right?
[Yeon-su] I knew it.
He doesn't remember at all.
Yes. I had something to give you
so I went to your place.
Hmm.
[Ung clears throat]
Then did I do something--
- [phone buzzing]
- Oh, sorry.
I need to get ready for the event.
The staff will tell you the details
regarding the live show
and everything else you need.
[Yeon-su] But seriously, there's no reason
for me to be avoiding him like this.
Hey.
Good luck.
Hmm.
[gentle music]
[door closes]
[Eun-ho sighs]
Oh, that's weird, you didn't run away.
[Eun-ho] Take a rest, it's okay.
We'll just rehearse later.
Here's the layout and program.
LIVE DRAWING SHOW
GO-OH
- Ms. Kook.
- Did you check Go-oh's video?
Yes, I did. Everything's fine.
I checked the whole thing just now.
Then go ahead and play it now, please,
alongside the playlist he's given us
- and put it on a loop.
- Yep.
["Christmas Tree" by V playing]
[Yeon-su] Unbelievable.
I've never seen that side of him before.
[Ye-in] Ms. Kook.
Ms. Kook.
[Eun-ho] Ung, we need to head out.
Are you asleep?
You feeling a little tense?
Do you want some more Xanax?
Why…
Why did I sleep well last night?
You say that like it's a problem.
Are you still hung up on that?
[Eun-ho] Yo, can you
write a caption for this?
Can you write,
"Pondering about what to draw"?
Make him look all mysterious.
[Ho] I think we can get a good view.
Is this his? Which one?
- No. It's the other one.
- This? Okay.
[Yeon-ok] Come on, let's go.
[guests chatting]
- I won't see anything from here.
- Just sit down.
- Come on.
- Let's sit at the front, right there.
Nu-a is here.
- [applause]
- [cheering]
Hello. It's nice to meet you all.
I'm honored to be able
to draw the buildings
designed by my role model, Jean Ferrat,
more so in a setting such as this.
I'm sure you're all aware,
that another artist will be drawing
on the other side in parallel with me.
- So if you're curious, go ahead and peek.
- [crowd laughing]
[Nu-a] However, since you're already here,
I doubt any of you will.
I guarantee you'll be
too immersed to move.
I'll be doing my absolute best
to win your hearts as an illustrator.
So now, ladies and gentlemen, I'm Nu-a.
[applause]
- Hey, son!
- [gasps]
[whispers from audience]
[Ho] That's my son.
- [man 1] He's so good.
- [man 2] Didn't think he'd be this tall.
["Christmas Tree" by V playing]
♪ In this moment ♪
♪ I see you ♪
♪ It always comes around as I believed ♪
♪ When the rain stops ♪
♪ You shine on me ♪
♪ Your light's the only thing
That keeps the cold out ♪
♪ Moon in the summer night ♪
♪ Whispering of the stars ♪
♪ They're singing like ♪
♪ Christmas trees for us ♪
♪ So I'll tell you ♪
♪ A million tiny things that ♪
♪ You have never known ♪
♪ It all gets tangled up inside ♪
♪ And I'll tell you ♪
♪ A million little reasons ♪
♪ I'm falling for your eyes ♪
♪ I just want to be where you are ♪
♪ Tell you ♪
♪ A million tiny things that ♪
♪ You have never known ♪
♪ It all gets tangled up inside ♪
♪ Tell you ♪
♪ A million little reasons ♪
♪ I'm falling for your eyes ♪
[Ji-ung] First time, huh?
- ♪ I just want to be where you are ♪
- Uh-huh.
I didn't know there was this side to him.
[chuckles softly]
He's like a different guy.
[Ji-ung chuckles]
Same here.
He looked like a total stranger
the first time I saw him drawing.
You're right.
By the way, good job.
This is quite a large-scale operation.
Must've been a pain to prepare this.
No, really. All part of the work.
Shouldn't you be working somewhere
instead of chatting with me?
Exactly. I'm here to pick you up, Yeon-su.
You can never judge a book by its cover.
Who knew I'd be working side by side
with the lowest scoring kid?
Obviously, he was
a nuisance all throughout.
As you all know, we're incompatible.
He and I are strikingly different.
Of course,
he's the annoying and frustrating type.
During this project, he should've
shared his progress with me,
so we'd be up to speed
to make things more efficient.
But he never said a single word.
Always just thinking to himself.
He was always like that
from the beginning.
I'd ask what was on his mind and it's,
"I don't know. Not sure.
There's nothing to say."
Either one of those.
Great, I'm getting annoyed all over again.
ANYTHING POSITIVE TO SAY ABOUT HIM?
Nothing at all.
Well…
NOT EVEN ONE?
I guess seeing him draw like that
for the first time kind of…
it was like discovering
a new side of him I never noticed before.
I mean, yes,
he used to draw a lot back then,
but he never had
that serious look on his face before.
I don't know what's gotten into him,
but he's completely focused,
like he's in his element.
Very different from the guy I know.
But you know what?
He was always serious about drawing,
it was his passion.
If you check back,
I think it was in episode five,
I accidentally ruined his drawing once,
and he threw
a massive fit for days, like I hurt him.
Honestly, I really did
feel bad about it. I did.
But seeing him
all worked up was kind of entertaining.
I mean, he rarely gets mad, you know.
He's always so quiet.
I admit that I did tease him
a few more times
to get a reaction for fun.
[chuckles]
He always made me laugh either way.
["Drawer" by 10cm playing]
Uhm…
Yeah, basically
I'm not used to this side of him.
I guess, it feels like he's changed.
Funny, I thought he'd never change.
Uhm, sorry, I was just rambling, wasn't I?
Let's cut that.
- Okay, next question.
- Hmm.
["Drawer" by 10cm continues]
Huh. Shouldn't he
take a breather or something?
Nah, this is how he always works.
All in till the end.
But since there's an audience,
he probably feels even more tense.
Good point. Let me go check up on him.
- Honey, let's go.
- All right.
Oh, wow. Is that you, Yeon-su?
Hello, glad you're here.
It's been ages since we saw each other.
I heard you were
part of this project from the others.
Yes. So how have you been lately?
It's always the same for us.
Nothing's really changed.
Goodness gracious. It's like
you haven't changed at all since then.
Same goes for the both of you.
Is it because of what we're wearing?
Are you here to watch Ung's drawing show?
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Then how come you're leaving already?
Oh. It's kind of dragging, right?
- No.
- [Yeon-ok] That's not why.
[Yeon-ok] Seeing him draw all alone
like that, makes us feel uncomfortable.
It reminds me
of the time when he was young.
To think even back then
it was so normal for him--
- [Ho] We should get going, come on.
- Okay.
Hey, Yeon-su,
come over for a meal sometime.
- You know you're always welcome.
- Okay.
No need to think about it too much,
just come on over.
Don't worry, it's free of charge.
He's right. You should come visit us.
I'll make you something good.
- Come, come.
- I'll be seeing you, okay?
[Yeon-ok chuckles]
It's just that…
the break-up devastated Ung.
It must have been hard for you too.
[gentle music]
We really want you to visit us.
So please, come and drop by, okay?
Okay. I will.
All right. Goodbye.
Mm-hmm.
Come on. We have to go, Yeon-su.
- Okay, okay.
- Hurry up.
- Goodbye.
- Stop dragging your feet.
Bye.
[gentle music]
[sighs]
[gentle music continues]
- Ji-ung.
- Hm?
Did you do the interview with Yeon-su?
Yeah. And the shoot?
There's nothing to film, so…
Not like we'll get much,
he's been sitting down for hours.
Go back to the office with Tae-hun,
start preparing for the meeting.
Don't wait for me.
I'll wrap things up over here.
[Yeon-ok] It's just that
the break-up devastated Ung.
[deep exhale]
["Maybe If" by BIBI playing]
[Ung] Wanna sleep over?
Are you sick? Do you have a fever?
[Yeon-su] How many pills
did you take anyway?
Do you take them often?
Huh? When did you start taking them?
Since when did you have trouble sleeping?
Why didn't you tell me much sooner?
[Yeon-su gasps softly]
["Maybe If" by BIBI continues]
[knocking]
Yes?
[Ye-in] Oh, someone told me
that you were here.
Everything's going well. In fact,
Nu-a's finishing up his piece now.
Uh, escort him to the first floor.
Get him all set up and prepped
for the press conference when he's done.
Stay with him there.
I'll escort Go-oh myself.
Got it, Ms. Kook.
[deep breath]
[Ung] I still have a bit of time left.
[surprised whispering]
Hello, everyone.
My name is Go-oh.
- [applause]
- [loud cheering]
[audience cheering]
Oh…
Hey, you. Congratulations.
You look a little different today.
[awkward chuckle]
[reporter] Wow, it's NJ!
[audience talking excitedly]
[cameras clicking rapidly]
[reporters clamoring]
[slow somber music]
[reporters continue clamoring]
- [reporter] NJ.
- [cameras continue clicking]
[slow somber music]
GO-OH, NU-A
SOEN SHOP OPENING DRAWING SHOW
How's it going, Ms. Kook?
How's everything?
It must have been a long day.
Thank you so much for your work today.
There's an after-party later, so feel free
to come, you're all invited to attend.
Uh, I'll just wrap things up over here.
You can all go.
Are you sure?
We can help you wrap up, we don't mind.
It's okay. You had to work on the weekend.
You deserve to relax. Thank you. Go.
Are you also coming to the after-party?
I don't know yet. We'll see. Go ahead.
All right, you have a good day, then.
- Hope to see you later.
- You have to come, you deserve it too.
[groans]
[somber music]
[sighs]
Why the hell
isn't that jackass picking up his phone?
Ung, over here! Come.
[Ung] Hey, why weren't you picking up?
Hey, stranger.
All done with the press conference?
NJ! What are you still doing here?
Oh, I guess you're not excited to see me.
Watch what you say next time,
you ungrateful fool.
She personally made time
to see you all the way out here.
Uh. Thank you so much
for coming to watch me.
I didn't expect you to come here.
I didn't think I'd come
uninvited to an event,
just to see someone either.
I actually arrived late
'cause of my schedule, but I still came.
Gotta say, you looked different out there.
NJ, I'll make extra sure
to send you an invite next time.
Oh, right. Just a heads up,
in case you get all flustered
seeing your name in
the top trending list in a few minutes,
I told the reporters it's nothing weird.
We're just two good friends
rooting for each other,
so don't worry about anything.
- Good friends?
- Well, yeah. Aren't we?
Well, we… no, I…
Yeah, of course we are.
I'm just kinda flattered
you consider me as a friend.
You're the first guy ever
- who's happy to be friend-zoned by me.
- What?
[gasps]
Never mind.
Are you going home? Do you need a ride?
It's okay.
We drove here as well. We'll be fine.
Okay. You take care now.
Sorry? Hold on.
Is that the only reason
you were waiting for me?
I already told you.
I'm very busy, but also I'm not.
- Take care.
- Have a safe trip.
Take care of yourself!
Hey, Ung, how could you
decline her offer? What are you nuts?
I'm exhausted. Shut up.
- Anyway, this is pretty huge.
- What is?
Today, you finally revealed yourself
to the adoring public,
not to mention
instantly winning everyone's hearts.
Bullshit. Just go and get the car, please.
So by extension, this pretty much means
that you've agreed to give me a big raise.
Shut up. I said, go and get the car.
This was from NJ, right?
- Oh, my God, it smells different.
- [both chuckle]
Go-oh has finally debuted!
[cheers]
[soft music]
[exhales]
That's sweet.
God, you're so pathetic.
Can't believe you're here to pity party
on such a freaking great day.
What are you talking about?
I came in case you were bored.
You got the bad juju.
Probably why this place is failing.
You should be at that party
celebrating the fact
that the project was a success!
You actually passed with flying colors,
but instead, you're here sulking.
- I like this more.
- This is beyond being pathetic.
Aren't you ecstatic all that hard work
you've been doing paid off?
Uh, not really. It's all just work.
Now that we're done,
it's on to the next project.
Things really tough at work?
No. It's actually easier
compared to my old job.
Yeah, I guess it's pretty good.
Then what's the problem?
It's not demanding enough to challenge me,
not exactly fun either.
- That's all. Pretty much.
- [glass clanks]
[clicks tongue]
Have another.
Remember what you said?
You said that my eyes
looked empty and soulless.
There was nothing in them.
Hmm. They're still the same.
So empty that the fish I've got back there
have livelier eyes than you.
Well, I saw this look in Ung's eyes
as he was drawing today.
They seemed so animated.
Like they were so full of life.
Really?
Hmm.
He was so focused on his drawing,
you could feel all his passion.
To be honest, I was jealous.
[scoffs]
What exactly would you be jealous of?
[chuckles softly]
Do I sound pathetic?
[chuckles]
I always hated people
that I thought were pathetic.
While he was working on improving himself,
there I was, stagnant
and busy making ends meet
with the soulless eyes of mine.
Yup. Even I would think I'm pathetic.
Christ. You're ridiculous.
You weren't stagnating,
let alone being soulless.
Think of the debt you had to pay off.
Now that was tough,
I saw how hard you worked.
Those are wins in life.
And you've succeeded
by coming this far, you fool.
[chuckles softly]
Tonight I'm going to celebrate
a successful project.
So consider me as your VIP.
Line up the soju bottles.
- Okay, I already put nine on your tab.
- Really?
Don't worry,
I'll be ripping you off all night.
- Oh. Good evening.
- [man] Hello, good evening.
- [woman] Where?
- [man] Over here?
- [Sol-i] Thank you.
- [woman] Okay.
[sighs]
[soft gentle music]
- [Sol-i] Here's the menu.
- [man] What's today's special?
- [Sol-i] Today, it's jjamppong rice.
- [woman] I'll have the bibimpap. No wait…
[groans]
Hey, Ung, good work today.
I'm going home. You get some good rest.
Hmm.
Hey. On your way out,
can you turn off that light?
All right. See ya.
Hmm.
[Ung groans]
[switch clicks]
[sighs]
[groans softly]
[phone buzzing]
[soft music]
- [indistinct chatter]
- [glasses clinking]
[Sol-i] And here's your order.
- I'll take the empty bottles.
- [man] Okay.
Hey, you're here.
Sorry for calling out of the blue.
I'm sure you know,
I'm pretty much the only friend she has.
Unfortunately, I'm too busy tonight
I can't get rid of her myself.
I can't hand her over
to the police either.
She'll get mad when she wakes up.
Actually, who really cares.
Take her.
Yeah. One minute, please.
[soft gentle music]
That you, Ung?
[gasps]
That's so cold.
[Ji-ung] You awake yet?
[groans in agreement]
- [yawns loudly]
- Didn't get enough rest?
Uh-huh.
On top of that,
I may have drunk a little bit.
- I'm a little drunk.
- Drink this.
Oh, how considerate.
[sips]
[gulps]
Sorry. What time is it?
Must have been a hassle.
Not really.
I was at a boring get-together.
- Did you drink too?
- A little bit.
But you're a lightweight.
- You remember that?
- [Yeon-su] Of course I do.
Like watching a grown man
who couldn't handle baby sips.
[scoffs]
Okay, that's a stretch.
[inhales]
By the way,
how's the documentary going anyway?
[breathes in sharply]
Well, it's going okay.
I regret agreeing to do it again
after all these years.
Back in high school, at least we were
young and cute, which was fine to watch.
But now all they're gonna get
is a bunch of adults working.
It'll just be boring.
[clicks tongue]
I'm afraid this whole thing
is gonna be a flop.
Sounds like wishful thinking on your part.
So? I'll make sure
no one ever gets to watch it.
You know how I am at promoting things.
- I'm going to spread a rumor.
- [chuckles]
[sniffs]
But if you agree to let me watch it first,
I might change my mind.
- You wanna watch it?
- I may have looked ugly in some shots
or blurted out
a swear word or two without realizing it.
I'm pretty sure that Ung
was talking crap about me all throughout.
Anyway, just curious. That's all.
By the way, what did Ung say about me?
Was it all bad?
I mean…
- [Yeon-su] Did he just shit-talk about--
- Hey…
You still like him, don't you?
[gentle music]
[Ji-ung] Hey.
You still like him, don't you?
[Yeon-su] No. That's impossible.
There's no way this is happening.
Choi Ung?
What are you doing out here so late?
I found out
that you moved back here recently.
I guess that's why
we kept running into each other.
Oh, I guess.
Did you have a drink?
What? Uh…
[clears throat]
Hmm.
I did. Anyway, what are you
doing out here? It's kinda late.
Yeah, I guess.
It was already late
when I got here earlier,
so I was debating
if maybe I should just go.
Uh…
If it's not that urgent,
maybe we can just talk next time?
I'm really tired right now.
[gasps]
[soft gentle music]
[light sweet music]
Hey, it's you again.
Am I dreaming?
I won't fall for it.
Yeon-su.
I've been in so much pain.
[Yeon-su] No, I remember all of it.
You okay? You seem pretty wasted.
No, I'm fine. I'm just tired.
You…
About last night…
Well, I saw a Thermos bottle at my house.
I was wondering if you left it there.
[Yeon-su] Thank God.
I'm glad he doesn't remember anything.
Yes. You kind of seemed like you were
out of it, so I just left it there.
Oh, really?
Mm-hmm. You were on some pills.
All dazed and stuff.
Did I fall asleep right after you left?
I think so.
Oh, okay then.
Did you come all the way here
to ask me that?
[awkward chuckle]
You could've just called.
Looks like
I'm the only one who'll remember.
I should go inside now.
See ya.
Guess I'll just take it to my grave.
[Ung] Tomorrow, you should
just pretend that you don't remember.
It wasn't a dream.
There's no need to lie.
So why pretend?
Yeon-su.
["There For You" by Kim Na Young playing]
Do you think this is right?
Do you think
what we're doing right now is right?
We're not like everyone else. We're us.
Our love for each other wasn't lukewarm…
and in the same way,
neither was our breakup.
It's been way too long.
We should be able to…
[soft sniffle]
…ask each other "How have you been?"
"How tough has it been for you?"
"It's been tough for me."
We're allowed to say those things.
[exhales deeply]
[Yeon-su] The reason we broke up…
How have you been?
…it was because I was arrogant.
Answer me.
How have you been, Yeon-su?
[Yeon-su] I was so arrogant,
I thought I could live…
without you.
["There For You"
by Kim Na Young continues]
PRIDE AND PREJUDICE
I'm going to keep that as a hobby.
[Ung] What I want
is to bask in the sun during the day
and lay underneath a lamp at night time.
A stressful life just isn't for me.
I'll be right back.
[sighs]
I sounded pathetic didn't I?
JOBS FOR DESIGN MAJORS
HOW EASY IS IT TO GET A JOB?
MAKING MONEY THROUGH DRAWING
4 MONTHS AFTER THE BREAKUP
♪ It always comes around as I believed ♪
♪ When the rain stops ♪
♪ You shine on me ♪
♪ Your light's the only thing
That keeps the cold out ♪
♪ Moon in the summer night ♪
♪ Whispering of the stars ♪
♪ They're singing like ♪
♪ Christmas trees for us ♪
♪ So I'll tell you ♪
♪ A million tiny things that ♪
♪ You have never known ♪
♪ It all gets tangled up inside ♪
♪ And I'll tell you ♪
♪ A million little reasons… ♪